# rameşaliyev

**Computer Scientist** 

I'm Ramesh, a former Software Engineer from Istanbul who mostly experienced in Web Technologies. I've worked in various companies as Lead and Senior Software Engineer. Currently I'm a Computer Science student at YTU. I'm interested in AI and mostly Computer Vision.

### education

BSc, Computer Science Yildiz Technical University (2019 - 2023)

ASc, Computer Programming Sakarya University (2016 - 2018)

High School, Electronics Zeytinburnu Industrial Vocational High School (2004 - 2007)

#### certifications

Fundamentals of Deep Learning NVIDIA, Deep Learning Institute (2021)

Data Science Math Skills Coursera, Duke University (2020)

## experiences

Undergraduate Research Fellow - Yildiz Technical University
Jun 2022 - Present

Co-Founder & Full Stack Developer - Ecma Co. Ltd. Jun 2017 - Jun 2021 (4 years)

Senior Full Stack Developer - Omma Sep 2018 - Nov 2020 (2 year 3 months)

Senior Frontend Developer - Pisano Feb 2018 - Sep 2018 (8 months)

Lead Full Stack Developer - Emlakjet Jan 2016 - Oct 2017 (1 year 10 months)

## Senior JavaScript Developer - Turkcell

Oct 2013 - Dec 2015 (2 years 3 months)

JavaScript Developer - E-NET Internet Technology Co.

Jan 2013 - Sep 2013 (9 months)

Frontend Developer - Techpoint Labs

Mar 2012 - Jan 2013 (11 months)

Full Stack Developer - Koridor Design Studio

Feb 2009 - Mar 2012 (3 years 2 months)

### links

rames.dev

github.com/ramesaliyev

linkedin.com/in/ramesaliyev

#### contact

ramesaliyev@gmail.com